{
    "subject": "resource/Felix_Hoffmann",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "German chemist",
    "human_readable": "Felix Hoffmann's description is 'German chemist'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5944949388504028,
            "question": "What contributions did Felix Hoffmann make to chemistry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5921891927719116,
            "question": "What nationality was Felix Hoffmann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5778228044509888,
            "question": "What kind of chemical research did Felix Hoffmann do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5722991228103638,
            "question": "Was Felix Hoffmann a scientist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5568314790725708,
            "question": "What profession did Felix Hoffmann have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44063451886177063,
            "question": "Where was Felix Hoffmann from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4381321966648102,
            "question": "Is there anything else notable about Felix Hoffmann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4164694547653198,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Felix Hoffmann's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40007495880126953,
            "question": "Were there any significant discoveries made by Felix Hoffmann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24253487586975098,
            "question": "In what time period did Felix Hoffmann live and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Felix Hoffmann's description is 'German chemist'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_700_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant discoveries made by Felix Hoffmann?",
            "html": "dbpedia_700_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Felix Hoffmann's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_700_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else notable about Felix Hoffmann?",
            "html": "dbpedia_700_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_700_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the value as \"yes\" or \"no\":\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Felix Hoffmann's description is indeed a \"German chemist\". The various files (e.g. file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_700/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt) describe Felix Hoffmann as a German chemist, notably for his major role in the discovery and development of an important class of drugs: nonsteroidal analgesics (NSAIDs)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents repeatedly describe Felix Hoffmann as a German chemist, supporting the statement that his description is 'German chemist'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}